sportsnewsminute.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy | SportsNewsMinute

Privacy Statement for SportsNewsMinute

SportsNewsMinute created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following data below discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for SportsNewsMinute.com.

**Advertisers**

We utilize 3rd Party Advertising Companies to display Ads/Banners on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our Advertisers. Please note that we do not have access to this information. 

**Policy For Minors**

SportsNewsMinute.com does not allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to register for our services. We may momentarily capture personally identifiable information for purposes of determining whether a user is over the age of thirteen (13) and thus qualifies to use our services. When the user is under the age of thirteen (13), submitted information is automatically deleted. 

**Public Forums**

This site contains links to other sites. SportsNewsMinute is not responsible for privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This site may link to chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups at times. Please remember that any information that is disclosed via these outlets become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may [contact us](http://www.sportsnewsminute.com/contact-us/) via e-mail.
